luuux.com 2012-12-26

# Privacy | LUUUX

### The LUUUX Privacy Policy

This privacy policy governs your use of the LUUUX software, the LUUUX service, the LUUUX websites and all other software, features, tools, websites, widgets, and services offered by or through LUUUX from PASSIONSFABRIKKEN APS and its business divisions.

By registering with LUUUX and using the LUUUX sites or products you will be providing LUUUX and PASSIONSFABRIKKEN APS with information which can personally identify you. These terms and conditions explain the policy related to this personally identifiable information.

### Collection of Your LUUUX Information

By registering and interacting with the LUUUX sites and products personally identifiable information will be collected or received and stored on our servers. This information may include e-mail addresses, information about your LUUUX site visits, page views, and contacts you may add into your friend’s lists, content you may add into the LUUUX sites, comments you may add to the LUUUX site or purchases you may make through the LUUUX stores or shops. Additional technical information may be also received and stored identifying the type of web browser used, the operating system, the IP address, the domain name or search engine from which the LUUUX site or products where accessed from and other information regarding the geographic location the LUUUX site or products may have been accessed from.

###  Use of LUUUX Information

We use Luuux information to manage and improve the features and functions of the LUUUX sites and products; for personalizing services and content; responding to your support and help enquiries and to offer services or products which may be of interest.  
Your LUUUX information will not be shared with 3rd parties except in circumstances with which you have agreed or in response to a legal request such as court order or subpoena, or in event that PASSIONSFABRIKKEN APS belief that LUUUX is being used for unlawful purposes.  
In event that PASSIONSFABRIKKEN APS belief it necessary to protect the rights or properties of LUUUX or PASSIONSFABRIKKEN APS LUUUX information may be disclosed.  
In the event that ownership of LUUUX was to change as a result of a merger or acquisition by another company, your LUUUX information may be transferred. PASSIONSFABRIKKEN APS will provide you notice prior to any such transfer of your LUUUX information.

### Cookies

PASSIONSFABRIKKEN APS may use cookies on the Websites it operates. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer's hard drive by our servers to identify your computer to our servers. No personally identifiable information stored in the LUUUX cookies will be shared with outside companies for any purpose without your permission.

### Minors and Children

LUUUX is intended for audiences of 15 or over and you are not permitted to register on the LUUUX site if you are under the age of 15. If you between the age of 15 and 18 years and not an emancipated minor, you should always consult your legal parents or guardian and get their permission before submitting personal information.

### 3rd Party Advertising Partners

LUUUX will carry advertising on its site from 3rd Party providers such as Google Ad Sense and other companies. We do not share you information with these companies, however, these companies may collect anonymous information about visits to LUUUX. In this section of our privacy policy, we include the names of our advertiser partners so you may contact them to opt-out of any anonymous site visit data they collect.  

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about the LUUUX Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us by sending an email to [support@LUUUX.com](mailto:support@LUUUX.com).

### Changes to this Privacy Policy and Additional Information

The LUUUX Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time, and so you should review this Policy periodically.

LUUUX may in the future offer other special features and services, and if these features and services are not described in this Policy, you will be provided with additional privacy-related information in this agreement.

15 February 2010
